Inventory of the Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
Vertical (Subject) Files, 1831 - [ongoing]
- Student Clubs and Activities
  - Wesleyan Science-Fiction and Fantasy Club
  - Wesleyan Serenaders
  - Wesleyan Shakespeare Society
  - Wesleyan Singers
  - Wesleyan Spirits
  - Wesleyan Womens Theater Collective
  - WesPeace
  - Wesleyan Prisoner Resource and Education Project (WesPREP)
  - Wes Radical Cheer Squad
  - WesRescue
  - WeSail/ Sailing club
  - WeShelter
  - WESTAND
  - WESU-Radio Station I
  - WESU-Radio Station II
  - WESU-Radio Station IProgram Schedules to 1990
  - WESU-Radio Station IIProgram Guides II 1990-
  - WESU-Radio Station Photos
  - WesWinds
  - WILDWes
  - William James Club Photos
  - Womanist House
  - Yacht Club
  - Zombie Art Collective
- Student Government
  - College Body Committee 1904-1963
  - College Body Committee 1963-1978
  - College Body SenatePhotos
  - Honors System 1893-
  - Judicial System
  - Student Assembly (WSA), 1978-
  - Student Budget Committee
- Student Publications
  - General
  - Academic Forum
  - Adlit
  - Advocate
  - The Air Scoop
  - Afrikan Nation
  - Anachnu
  - The Ankh
  - Aphorism
  - Araby
  - Argus
  - Avatar
  - Babel
  - Balls!
  - Betel Nut
  - A Better Bible
  - Beyondpartisan.org
  - Borders
  - Bound
  - Brainstormer
  - The Bull o Ten
  - The Bull Sheet
  - Campus Distort
  - The Campus Review
  - Cardinal
  - Celebrations
  - Chatreuse
  - The Clarion
  - Le Clairon
  - The Classic
  - A Closer Look
  - Contents Under Pressure
  - Corkboard
  - The Cricket
  - Cunt Conversations
  - Currents
  - The Daily Koan
  - Dialogue
  - The Diplomat
  - Disorientation (Hermes)
  - Diva
  - The Downey House Poets
  - Earth Action Journal
  - Echo
  - Echo Magazine (Spoken Word Poetry)
  - Entropy
  - Expression
  - Eye on Dance
  - Eyewash
  - Fat Bottom
  - Foco Latino
  - Fresh Semantics
  - Geek
  - The Glass Cannibal
  - Goose
  - Grail
  - Hamakkor
  - Handprint
  - Hangmans Lime
  - Hermes, 1930s-1940s
  - Hermes, 1975-
  - Historical Narratives
  - Iahu
  - Identity in Progress
  - Incite
  - In.d
  - Jar Magazine
  - Joybuzzer
  - Junctions
  - Kaleidoscope
  - Last Chance Noose
  - Logos
  - Loop
  - Magazine of English 161 & 262
  - Malignant Brain Humor
  - Merkin
  - Method
  - Mokita
  - Monkey and the Penguin
  - Mr Badman
  - New Dawn
  - Olla Podrida
  - The Organ
  - Ostranenic
  - Pataphysics
  - Pedestrian
  - Point 7
  - Politics and Education
  - Political Union News
  - Pool
  - Primer
  - Pro Archia
  - Quarterly
  - Ratito!
  - Reflection
  - Resonance
  - Rooster
  - Safety Valve
  - Scientists
  - 7x7
  - Small Antenna
  - Smut
  - Special Connections
  - Squids Eye View
  - Stillborn
  - Strike News
  - Synthesis
  - The Testing Digest
  - The Threepenny paper
  - The Tin Drum
  - Tweedledum
  - Typeface
  - The Undergraduate Journal of Social Studies
  - Village Vice
  - The Weasel
  - WEScrive
  - Wesley Antics
  - Wesleyan Adversary
  - Wesleyan Alternative Press
  - Wesleyan Alumni Courier
  - Wesleyan Argus Magazine
  - Wesleyan Critical Review
  - Wesleyan Economic Journal
  - The Wesleyan Enquirer
  - The Wesleyan Mind & Body
  - Wesleyan Music Journal
  - Wesleyan Public Affairs Quarterly
  - Wesleyan Public Affairs Review
  - Wesleyan Review, 1957
  - Wesleyan Review, 1969 Commentary, Criticism, Poetry, Art
  - Wesleyan Review, 1974-75 Supplement to the Argus
  - Wesleyan Review, 1981- Published by Wesleyan Republicans
  - Wesleyan Student Poets
  - Wesleyan Theatre Magazine
  - Wesleyan WASP
  - Wesleyan Writing
  - Wes Now News
  - Wesquire
  - Whats News in Economics
  - Writers Block
  - WSA Newsletter
- Trustees
  - TrusteesGeneral
  - TrusteesGroups
  - Adams, Charles
  - Bangs, Heman
  - Camp, Daniel W.
  - Chayes, Antonia Handler
  - Clark, Laban
  - Crittenden, Albert R.
  - Deitch, Jeffrey
  - Denison, Charles Land
  - Donaldson, William H.
  - Drew, Daniel
  - Gribbel, John
  - Hardy, John Wesley
  - Hubbard, Elijah
  - McWilliams, Mary Davidson
  - Mather, Thomas G.
  - Moe, Henry Allen
  - Rice, William
  - Rich, Issac
  - Rockwell, Charles L.
  - Sessions, William E.
  - Sillin, Lilan Flor
  - Sprague, Seth
  - Trench, William James
  - Wright, Mary Clabaugh